





+971 55 8780193 cyrilgmarcus@gmail.com



Dubai, UAE



linkedin.com/in/cyril-marcus/



github.com/brownkcing /
https://brownkcing.github.io/CGM/

#### EDUCATION

Self-taught developer.
Astrolab Coding Bootcamp
Certificate
December 2018

Aviation Service Certificate Emirates Aviation University

B.Sc (Hons.) Biotechnology UCSI University Incomplete 112/120 (credits) 2009 - 2014

## HARD SKILLS

Javascripts

Node JS - Express JS

MongoDB/Mongoose

React JS/React Native

Redux

RESTful

JSON - JQUERY

CSS

HTML

# CYRIL MARCUS

Full-stack Developer

### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A Malaysian national with 3 years' experience in aviation/administration. I am also a freelance web developer (full-stack on MERN) and currently shifting career full time to full-stack developer. Came from science research background, I am also a self-taught programmer and web developer. Teaching and learning myself on programming and its core fundamental back in 2016 until now. Always try to better myself and learn new things while accomplishing in otherwise challenging task. Currently based in Dubai.

### EXPERIENCES

Full-stack developer (Freelance)

Feb 2018 - CURRENT

This is more of a learning/work process that I did while learning the language on my own. While learning, I've done learning project from online platform such as Udemy, freecodecamp, Traversy Media, and also from coding bootcamp in Dubai, Astrolabs. Currently proficient in MERN stack, my full recent project was Initium, coauthor with Sophie Swart, a fellow developer.

(SENIOR) CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST | EMIRATES GROUP JUNE 2015 - CURRENT

Provide ground supports, customer-related services, and various technical task. Various task that are performed daily/weekly, and events or project done:

- Routine GH, pre/post flight operation handling.
- Ticketing/Reservation.
- Assist in company product development.
- Liaise in-between department for project development in airport operations.
- Addressing issues and handling customers' requests.
- Maintaining appropriate record and filing system.



## CYRIL MARCUS

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

## Knowledge of

Database

Git/Github

SEO

Semantic UI / Bootstrap

Webpack / Babel

ES5 - ES6, Learning on ES7

Microsoft Visual Studio Code

Prototype and MVP

Heroku

POSTMAN API

and many others

## Spoken Language

English (Native)

Malay

Japanese

## INTERESTS

Traveling

Coding

ΙT

Journalist

Music

# EXPERIENCE (Continued)

FINANCE ADMINISTRATOR | CARLSBERG MARKETING SDN BHD JULY 2014 - APRIL 2015

Performing daily accuracy checks and various task:

- Assist team leader on completing projects and closing accounts before the day ends
- Assist team leader in reviewing invoice-processes on daily basis
- Provide and assist in reporting SAP report weekly for sample checking
- Accuracy checks on clients contracts and amend any discrepancies in the contract as per database and with the advice of team leader

#### REFERENCES

AHMAD ABUGOSH | DIRECTOR OF MARKETING & LEARNING PROCESS ASTROLABS

ahmadabugosh.com github.com/ahmadabugosh

HUSSAM MOHSINEH | FOUNDING PARTNER & MVP MANAGEMENT
PROTOTYPE TUTOR
SAHEM.AE / ASTROLABS
hussam.mohsineh@gmail.com